<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ligtas</string>

    <string name="digits_number">1234567890+</string>

    <!--Gender-->
    <string-array name="gender">
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Male</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Yes or no-->
    <string-array name="yesno">
        <item>Yes</item>
        <item>No</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--User Type-->
    <string-array name="userType">
        <item>Student</item>
        <item>Professor</item>
        <item>Employee</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Covid 19 Vaccinated-->
    <string-array name="covid19">
        <item>First Dose</item>
        <item>Second Dose</item>
        <item>Booster</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Health Issue-->
    <string-array name="comorbidity">
        <item>Asthma</item>
        <item>Cancer</item>
        <item>Cardiovascular Disease</item>
        <item>Cerebro-stroke/Cerebrovascular Accident</item>
        <item>Chronic Kidney Disease</item>
        <item>Chronic Liver Disease</item>
        <item>Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease (COPD)</item>
        <item>Chronic Respiratory Tract Infection</item>
        <item>Diabetes Mellitus</item>
        <item>Down Syndrome</item>
        <item>Emphysema</item>
        <item>Hepatitis B</item>
        <item>Hypertension</item>
        <item>Immunodeficiency State</item>
        <item>Neurologic Disease</item>
        <item>Obesity (BMI of 30kg/m2 or higher)</item>
        <item>Tuberculosis</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_user_navigation">UserNavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--Navigation Menu-->
    <string name="menu_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="menu_generate_qr_code">Generate QR-code</string>
    <string name="menu_stay_healthy">Stay Healthy</string>
    <string name="menu_monitor_your_health">Monitor Your Health</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_terms_and_conditions">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="menu_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="menu_logout">Log out</string>

    <!--about ligtas-->
    <string name="about_ligtas">
        Ligtas is a Health Monitoring Mobile Application developed by the student researchers of Philippine State College
        of Aeronautics (PHILSCA) - Villamor Campus that aims to help the aviation community management to manage and
        monitor the user\'s health information.
    </string>

    <!--Terms and conditions-->
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
        Welcome to our Application developed by Philippine State College of Aeronautics (VAB) researchers.
        Suppose you continue to browse and use this Application. In that case, you agree to comply with and
        be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which, together with our privacy policy, govern
        our relationship with you concerning this Application. These Terms include all other policies, rules,
        and terms and conditions as outlined in Service materials from time to time, all of which are incorporated
        herein. I understand that my personal information is protected by RA 10173, Data Privacy Act of 2012 and
        that I am required to provide truthful information.

        \n\n<b>Condition of Use</b>\n\n
        We will provide this Application to you, which is subject to the conditions stated below in this document. Every time
        you visit this Application and use its service, you accept the following conditions. Therefore, we urge you to
        read and understand it carefully.
        Your use of any information or materials on this Application is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be
        liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services, or information available through
        this Application meet your specific requirements.

        \n\n<b>Copyright</b>\n\n
        This Application contains material that is owned by or licensed to us. It includes, but is not limited to, the contents,
        layout, design, colors, appearance, graphics, and imagery of the Mobile Application, Contents, and Materials, as well
        as copyrights, trademarks, and other intellectual property contained in the Mobile Application. All trademarks reproduced
        in this Application, which are not the property of, or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the Application.
        Unauthorized use of this Application may give rise to a claim for damages and be a criminal offense.

        \n\n<b>Linkage to third parties</b>\n\n
        From time to time, this Mobile Application may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your
        convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility
        for the content of the linked website(s).

        \n\n<b>Applicable Law</b>\n\n
        By visiting this Application, you agree that the laws of the Philippines, without regard to principles of conflict laws,
        will govern these terms and conditions or any dispute of any sort that might come between you or business partners and associates.
        By continuing to use our Application, you acknowledge that you have had the chance to review and consider these Terms and
        Conditions, and you acknowledge that you agreed to them. This means that you also consent to the use of your information
        and the method of disclosure as described in these Terms and Conditions. If you do not understand the Terms and Conditions
        or do not agree to them, then please do not use the Mobile Application.

    </string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">
        POLICY ON CONSENSUAL DATA COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION\n\n
        The System, accessible on desktop and mobile devices, intends to assist researchers in more correctly and efficiently managing, analyzing,
        and monitoring individual information. We guarantee user security and data privacy. As a result, we will only need what the System actually
        needs to work. If someone chooses to use our Service, they will be informed of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of
        Personal Information via this page.

        \n\n<b>WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM THE USER </b>\n\n
        Without your permission, we never collect any personal information.
        The Data Privacy Act of 2012, or Republic Act 10173, will be used to manage, preserve, and protect the personal information that the System collects.
        The System will only gather, use, or disclose your personal information in accordance with this policy and the Data Privacy Act of 2012.
        We only gather personal information for specific, legitimate objectives that have been decided upon and announced before or as soon as is practically
        possible after collection, which will only be processed later in a manner consistent with those declared, specific, and legitimate goals.

        \n\nThese are the following data needed upon using the Application:\n
        1.Type of User\n
        2.Name\n
        3.Full Address\n
        4.Email\n
        5.Gender\n
        6.Birthdate\n
        7.Mobile Number\n
        8.Password\n
        9.Health Status\n
        10.Comorbidity

        \n\n<b>COOKIES </b>\n\n
        Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as unique anonymous identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites you visit and
        stored on your device\'s internal memory.
        This Service does not use these \“cookies\” explicitly. However, the app may use third-party code and libraries that use \“cookies\” to collect information and
        improve their services. You can either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies,
        you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

        \n\n<b>WHAT WE DO WITH PERSONAL DATA AND COLLECTED DATA </b>\n\n
        This data would only be retained and used specifically for the purpose of Web Application.

        \n\n<b>HOW WE SECURE YOUR INFORMATION </b>\n\n
        We implement reasonable and appropriate physical, technical, and organizational measures to prevent your information\'s loss, destruction, misuse, or alteration.
        While there is no guarantee that information sent over the internet is fully secured, we keep and protect your information using a secured server behind a firewall,
        encryption, and security controls.
        Your Personal Data and Collected Data are protected by technical, organizational, and physical safeguards that keep them safe against destruction, unauthorized access,
        alteration, disclosure, fraudulent usage, and/or any other illegal processing, as well as any natural and man-made hazards.

        \n\n <b>CONTACT US </b>\n\n
        If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at:\n
        Email: ligtas.healthmonitoring@gmail.com\n
        Last Updated: November 4, 2022.
    </string>


</resources>